<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Process on Tri Wall</title>
    <link>https://mmadanguit.github.io/art-attack/process/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Process on Tri Wall</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://mmadanguit.github.io/art-attack/process/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Budget</title>
      <link>https://mmadanguit.github.io/art-attack/process/budget/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmadanguit.github.io/art-attack/process/budget/</guid>
      <description>Budget Breakdown When planning our deliverable we decided that we wanted to create the largest sculpture that we could make. We determined the two biggest blockers that we were going to run into were time and budget. To overcome the issue of budget we spent a lot of time figuring out the most cost effective components and implementations for each subsystem before purchasing anything for the project. This can be seen in our budget spreadsheet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sprint 1</title>
      <link>https://mmadanguit.github.io/art-attack/process/sprint1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmadanguit.github.io/art-attack/process/sprint1/</guid>
      <description>Project Goals Our team came together with a desire to see more art at Olin and create something cool and creative. This gave rise to our overarching project goal, which was to create a large-scale, impactful installation that has a well integrated system capable of generating engaging patterns of movement. We wanted to create something that could excite and last within the Olin community, and found inspiration in sculptures that change and respond to the presence of a person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sprint 2</title>
      <link>https://mmadanguit.github.io/art-attack/process/sprint2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmadanguit.github.io/art-attack/process/sprint2/</guid>
      <description>We spent our second sprint working on building out the wall to a 1x1 meter grid.
Mechanical Our mechanical team made the decision to 3D print and laser cut all the parts, and worked on optimizing the printer settings to print as many parts as possible in shorter time.
Electrical Our electrical team worked on an arduino board mount to fit and control all 3 servo controllers. They also created wires and a system for wire management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sprint 3</title>
      <link>https://mmadanguit.github.io/art-attack/process/sprint3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmadanguit.github.io/art-attack/process/sprint3/</guid>
      <description>If sprints had catch phrases, Sprint 3’s catch phrase would be “quit while you’re ahead”. In this sprint we decided to reevaluate our final deliverable and scale back where we could. At this point, we had poured almost 48 hours into the crochet alone and it was clear that if we were going to make the full 1x3 meter sculpture we were hoping to make, we would have to treat this project like a 9-5 job until it was due which wasn’t going to be possible with everyone’s busy schedules.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
